<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brian Joseff</title>
    <link>www.brianjoseff.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Brian Joseff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 23:34:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="www.brianjoseff.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>my first post</title>
      <link>www.brianjoseff.com/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 23:34:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.brianjoseff.com/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>The Nellie, a cruising yawl, swung to her anchor without a flutter of the sails, and was at rest. The flood had made, the wind was nearly calm, and being bound down the river, the only thing for it was to come to and wait for the turn of the tide.
The sea-reach of the Thames stretched before us like the beginning of an interminable waterway. In the offing the sea and the sky were welded together without a joint, and in the luminous space the tanned sails of the barges drifting up with the tide seemed to stand still in red clusters of canvas sharply peaked, with gleams of varnished sprits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>test post</title>
      <link>www.brianjoseff.com/posts/test-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 23:55:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.brianjoseff.com/posts/test-post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bangbang</title>
      <link>www.brianjoseff.com/bangbang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.brianjoseff.com/bangbang/</guid>
      <description>What is Bangbang? Helping people take action on things they care about.
Find ways to take action, share what you do without judgement, discuss what needs to be done, build community around your interests, mobilize other people to do things.
Go to site... What&#39;s the point? Everyone is asking us to take action. Who should we listen to? What should we do? How do we do it? What things actually will have an impact?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bedrock</title>
      <link>www.brianjoseff.com/bedrock/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.brianjoseff.com/bedrock/</guid>
      <description>What is Bedrock? We are building a new type of digital machine. Something powerful, private, and radically yours. Designed from the ground up to protect, empower, and respect you.
Go to site&amp;hellip;
Why we are building this It&amp;rsquo;s time for a Spaceship for the Mind.
“Bicycles for the mind” was a nice idea in 1979.
But we’ve now pedaled our way into darkness.
Those Bicycles have turned into corporate controlled exercise bikes that we pedal pedal furiously in some dark, meaningless rat race.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strength In Diversity</title>
      <link>www.brianjoseff.com/strength_in_diversity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.brianjoseff.com/strength_in_diversity/</guid>
      <description>What is Strength in Diversity? We bring together people from different worlds to connect, learn from each other, and elevate each other.
Our core program is a mixed-income, mixed-race community of people living together in East Palo Alto, CA and helping each other make strides in creative careers.
Go to site... Why is this important? Society is unequal. This inequality leads to hatred, violence, and loss of productivity. Unequal opportunity is also morally wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>